# Dylan Kane

London, E1 4BJ dkane6112@gmail.com

#### +447873895035

I am a motivated, hardworking IT support technician currently studying Computer Science at Queen Mary University. I have expertise in maintaining computer systems, providing technical support, and ensuring data security whilst working to deadlines in high-pressure environments. I excel at collaborating with colleagues to achieve goals but also have the initiative to problem solve by myself. I have a keen interest in software development, specifically building web services and apps using various web technologies, and I have taken relevant online courses to gain skills in this area.

Work Experience

#### IT Technician

Notley High School Sep 2022 to Sep 2023

- Maintained and updated computer hardware, software, and network systems using different software such as Microsoft Admin, Active directory
- Provided 1<sup>st</sup> 2<sup>nd</sup> and 3<sup>rd</sup> line technical support to staff, students and parents. troubleshooting problems amongst a wide variety of different hardware and software in person, over the phone and using software to remote into computers
- Ensured data security and integrity by managing firewalls, as well as backup and recovery systems
- Provided training to teaching staff on how to use a new classroom management software, frequently helped student to learn different software applications, tools and basic computer skills
- Set up audio-visual equipment for presentations and managed the school's website and online presence
- Manage and maintain data in the schools MIS; Fixed a major data integrity issue that was having an impact on a lot of different software
- · Utilised schools ticketing software providing help to users within the SLA

## **IT Technician**

**RDC** - Braintree

Jan 2022 to Sep 2022

- Data erasure
- Data entry
- Using Microsoft Office software especially excel
- Quality checks and repairs on a wide range of devices: PC, Laptops, Tablets, Mac & Windows, Cisco servers
- Using email effectively to communicate between departments

## Education

# **BSc Computer Science**

Queen Mary University of London

Present

## Access to Higher Education (Computer Science and Mathematics)

Equivalent to 3 A levels (134 UCAS Points)

Stonebridge College

October 2021 to July 2023

## Skills

- · Skilled with Java and Kotlin
- Familiar with JavaScript and other web and app technologies such as HTML, CSS, Spring Boot, SDK
- Proficient with databases MySQL and Microsoft Access
- · Strong problem-solving skills
- · Ability to work well in a team environment
- · Excellent communication skills
- · Skilled with whole Microsoft Office especially Excel
- · Proven track record of providing technical support and great customer service
- · Familiar with Linux systems